Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  - HarnMaster
    - Shek-Pvar. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1990., D04382907X (Box BG 39, Volume 1188)
  - HarnWorld
    - Harn: A Brilliant and Unique Fantasy World. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1983., D04403639T (Box BG 39, Volume 1461)
    - The Seven Major Cities of Harn. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1983., D04382897+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1195)
    - Melderyn. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1987., D04382910R (Box BG 39, Volume 1182)
    - Pilots' Almanac. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1988., D04382911S (Box BG 39, Volume 1183)
    - Azadmere: Dwarven Kingdom. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1989., D04382909Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1181)
    - Kiraz: The Lost City. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1989., D04382912T (Box BG 39, Volume 1184)
    - HarnWorld: A Real Fantasy World, 2nd ed.. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1990., D04403637R (Box BG 39, Volume 1459)
    - HarnWorld: A Real Fantasy World, 2nd edition. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1990., D04403634O (Box BG 39, Volume 1448)
    - Shorkyne: Regional Expansion Module. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1991., D04403638S (Box BG 39, Volume 1460)
    - Castles of Orbaal. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1992., D04383073S (Box BG 39, Volume 1449)
    - Curse of Hlen. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1993., D04382908Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1185)
    - HarnPlayer: a Player's Guide to Harnworld. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1994., D04403623M (Box BG 39, Volume 1447)
  - Haven
    - City of The Sacred Flame. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04403919U (Box BG 39, Volume 1737)
    - Lait of the Freebooters. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04403920M (Box BG 39, Volume 1738)
    - Secrets of the Labyrinth. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04403917S (Box BG 39, Volume 1735)
    - Within the Tyrant's Demesne. Published by Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd., 1983., D04403918T (Box BG 39, Volume 1736)
  - Hero Games
    - Star Hero: A Science Fiction Role Playing Game (#50). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04563802S (Box BG 39, Volume 2099)
    - Widows & Orphans. Published by Hero Games, 1997., D04405970T (Box BG 39, Volume M6)
  - Hero System
    - Hero System: The Ultimate Gamer's Toolkit, 5th edition. Published by San Francisco, CA: DOJ Inc., 2002., D04254495X (Box BG 39, Volume 43)
    - Until Defenders of Freedom. Published by San Francisco, CA: DOJ Inc., 2003., D04254493V (Box BG 39, Volume 41)
    - Until Superpowers Database. Published by San Francisco, CA: DOJ Inc., 2003., D04254494W (Box BG 39, Volume 42)
    - Champions Worldwide. Published by San Francisco, CA: DOJ Inc., 2005., D04254492U (Box BG 39, Volume 40)
  - Hero Wars
    - Glorantha: Introduction to the Hero Wars. Published by Oakland, CA: Issaries, Inc., 2000., D04382370R (Box BG 39, Volume 739)
    - Hero Wars: Roleplaying in Glorantha. Published by Oakland, CA: Issaries, Inc., 2000., D04382369Z (Box BG 39, Volume 740)
  - High Fantasy
    - Fortress Ellendar. Published by Indianapolis, IN: Fantasy Productions, Inc., 1979., D04382830S (Box BG 39, Volume 1068)
    - High Fantasy. Published by Indianapolis, IN: Fantasy Productions, Inc., 1979., D04382832U (Box BG 39, Volume 1070)
    - Moorguard. Published by Indianapolis, IN: Fantasy Productions, Inc., 1979., D04382831T (Box BG 39, Volume 1069)
  - Hollow World
    - Nightrage. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382477Z (Box BG 39, Volume 851)
    - Nightwail. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382476Y (Box BG 39, Volume 852)
    - Kingdom of Nithia. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382452S (Box BG 39, Volume 824)
    - Nightstorm. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382478- (Box BG 39, Volume 850)
    - Sons of Azca. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382485Y (Box BG 39, Volume 858)
    - The Milenian Empire. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382451R (Box BG 39, Volume 823)
    - The Milenian Scepter. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382479. (Box BG 39, Volume 849)
  - In Nomine
    - Feast of Blades. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1997., D04403628R (Box BG 39, Volume 1451)
    - In Nomine. Published by Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games, 1997., D04382713S (Box BG 39, Volume 1358)
  - Indiana Jones
    - Indiana Jones and the Rising Sun. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1994., D04382121L (Box BG 39, Volume 234)
    - Raiders of the Lost Ark Sourcebook. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1994., D04254447U (Box BG 39, Volume 232)
    - Indiana Jones and the Golden Vampires. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1995., D04254448V (Box BG 39, Volume 233)
    - Indiana Jones and the Lands of Adventure. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1995., D04254449W (Box BG 39, Volume 235)
    - Indiana Jones and the Tomb of the Templars. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1995., D04254450O (Box BG 39, Volume 236)
    - Indiana Jones Adventures. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1996., D04254452Q (Box BG 39, Volume 238)
    - Indiana Jones and the Sky Pirates and Other Tales. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1996., D04254455T (Box BG 39, Volume 241)
    - Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1996., D04254453R (Box BG 39, Volume 239)
    - Indiana Jones Artifacts. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1996., D04254451P (Box BG 39, Volume 237)
    - Indiana Jones Magic and Mysticism: The Dark Continent. Published by Honesdale, PA: West End Games, 1997., D04254454S (Box BG 39, Volume 240)
  - Islandian Campaign
    - Brotherhood of the Bolt. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403770P (Box BG 39, Volume 1582)
    - Gems for Death. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403750N (Box BG 39, Volume 1581)
    - Plague of Terror. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403771Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1583)
    - Streets of Gems. Published by Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc., 1983., D04403768W (Box BG 39, Volume 1578)
  - James Bond 007
    - Q Manual: The Illustrated Guide to the World's Finest Armory. Published by New York, NY: Victory Games, Inc., 1983., D03574348Y (Box BG 39, Volume 593)
    - Thrilling Locations. Published by New York, NY: Victory Games, Inc., 1985., D03574345V (Box BG 39, Volume 594)
  - Jovian Chronicles
    - Jovian Chronicles. Published by Montreal, Canada: Ianus Publications, 1993., D04563949/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2203)
    - Europa Incident. Published by Montreal, Canada: Ianus Publications, 1994., D04563950W (Box BG 39, Volume 2204)
    - Advanced Rules and Background. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1997., D04563943Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2197)
    - Mechanical Catalog: Exo-Armors and Spacecraft. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1997., D04563942X (Box BG 39, Volume 2196)
    - Rules and Background for Jovian Chronicles: Enter the Saga of Mankind. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1997., D04563944Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2198)
    - Chaos Principle: Original Cinematic Adventure. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1998., D04563941W (Box BG 39, Volume 2195)
    - Game Aid for Jovian Chronicles. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1998., D04563879% (Box BG 39, Volume 2194)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume One: Jovian Confederation. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1998., D04563948$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2202)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1999., D04563878+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2193)
    - Lightning Strike Supplement One: Venus: Behind the Veil. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1999., D04563877/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2192)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Three: Cega Navy. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1999., D04563946. (Box BG 39, Volume 2200)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Two: Jovian Confederation. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1999., D04563947 (Box BG 39, Volume 2201)
    - Solapol Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 1999., D04563939$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2189)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike, Second Edition. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563936- (Box BG 39, Volume 2186)
    - Earth: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563937. (Box BG 39, Volume 2187)
    - Jupiter: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563938 (Box BG 39, Volume 2188)
    - Lightning Strike Supplement Two: Call to Arms. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563876$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2191)
    - Mechanical Catalog Two: Civilian Equipment and Spacecraft. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563940V (Box BG 39, Volume 2190)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Four: Venus Fleet. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563945- (Box BG 39, Volume 2199)
    - Space Equipment Handbook: Advanced Tools & Weapons. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2000., D04563935Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2185)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike Companion. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2001., D04563931V (Box BG 39, Volume 2181)
    - Nomads: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2001., D04563932W (Box BG 39, Volume 2182)
    - Shadow of Cega: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2001., D04563934Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2184)
    - Spacer's Guide: A Guide to Life in the Twenty-Third Century. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2001., D04563933X (Box BG 39, Volume 2183)
    - Mars: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2002., D04563929 (Box BG 39, Volume 2179)
    - Venus: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2002., D04563930U (Box BG 39, Volume 2180)
    - Cislunar Space: Planet Sourcebook. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2003., D04563928. (Box BG 39, Volume 2178)
    - Jovian Chronicles RPG Player's Handbook, Second Edition. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2003., D04563926Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2176)
    - Roleplaying Core Rules: Silhouette Core, Version 003. Published by Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9, 2003., D04563927- (Box BG 39, Volume 2177)
  - Justice
    - Trail of the Gold Spike. Published by San Mateo, CA: Hero Games, 1984., D04563847. (Box BG 39, Volume 2115)
    - Aaron Allston's Lands of Mystery. Published by San Mateo, CA: Hero Games, 1985., D04563819- (Box BG 39, Volume 2110)
  - Kingdom Module
    - Kaldor. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1986., D04382891Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1198)
    - Kanday. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1986., D04382893. (Box BG 39, Volume 1200)
    - Chybisa. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1987., D04382892- (Box BG 39, Volume 1199)
    - Menglana. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1987., D04382896/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1202)
    - Orbaal. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1987., D04382894 (Box BG 39, Volume 1201)
  - Lankhmar
    - Lankhmar: City of Adventure. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382322O (Box BG 39, Volume 667)
    - Swords of the Undercity. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382321N (Box BG 39, Volume 666)
    - Swords of Deceit. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382320M (Box BG 39, Volume 665)
    - Nehwon. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382318T (Box BG 39, Volume 663)
    - Thieves of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382319U (Box BG 39, Volume 664)
    - Wonders of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382316R (Box BG 39, Volume 661)
    - Prince of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382317S (Box BG 39, Volume 662)
    - Tales of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382315Q (Box BG 39, Volume 660)
    - Slayers of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382295X (Box BG 39, Volume 630)
    - City of Adventure. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D03574343T (Box BG 39, Volume 626)
    - Rogues in Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382294W (Box BG 39, Volume 629)
    - Avengers in Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382292U (Box BG 39, Volume 627)
    - Cutthroats of Lankhmar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382293V (Box BG 39, Volume 628)
  - Legend of the Five Rings
    - Game Master's Pack. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D04382225Q (Box BG 39, Volume 507)
    - Honor's Veil. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D04382224P (Box BG 39, Volume 506)
    - Roleplaying in the Emerald Empire. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D03805800O (Box BG 39, Volume 503)
    - The Book of the Shadowlands: The Writings of Kuni Mokuna. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D03805796 (Box BG 39, Volume 502)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 1: The Way of the Dragon. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D03805801P (Box BG 39, Volume 496)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 2: The Way of the Unicorn. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1996., D03805802Q (Box BG 39, Volume 497)
    - Code of Bushido. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D04382223O (Box BG 39, Volume 505)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 3: The Way of the Crab. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D03805803R (Box BG 39, Volume 498)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 4: The Way of the Crane. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D03805807V (Box BG 39, Volume 499)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 6: The Way of the Lion. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D03805799+ (Box BG 39, Volume 501)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 5: The Way of the Scorpion. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D03805798/ (Box BG 39, Volume 500)
    - The Way of the Phoenix. Published by Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D03574347X (Box BG 39, Volume 617)
    - Twilight Honor. Published by Alderac Entertainment Group, 1998., D04382222N (Box BG 39, Volume 504)
  - Marvel Super Heroes
    - Avengers Assembled!. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382792Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1127)
    - Cat's-Paw. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382849 (Box BG 39, Volume 1147)
    - Judge's Screen: A Hero's Guide to New York. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382773Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1128)
    - Lone Wolves. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382850U (Box BG 39, Volume 1148)
    - Murderworld!. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382851V (Box BG 39, Volume 1149)
    - Secret Wars. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382984 (Box BG 39, Volume 1293)
    - The Breeder Bombs. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382853X (Box BG 39, Volume 1151)
    - Time Trap. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382852W (Box BG 39, Volume 1150)
    - Concrete Jungle: Official Character Roster. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382774Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1129)
    - Fault Line. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382846Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1144)
    - New York, New York. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382775- (Box BG 39, Volume 1130)
    - Project: Wideawake: Official Character Roster. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382776. (Box BG 39, Volume 1131)
    - The Last Resort. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382847- (Box BG 39, Volume 1145)
    - Thunder Over Jotunheim. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382848. (Box BG 39, Volume 1146)
    - Weapons Locker. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382854Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1152)
    - Secret Wars II. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382791Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1126)
  - MegaTraveller
    - MegaTraveller Players' Manual. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1987., D04382873Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1169)
    - Gazelle Class: Close Escort. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1989., D04383031M (Box BG 39, Volume 1356)
    - Laboratory Ship. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1989., D04383042O (Box BG 39, Volume 1370)
    - Subsidized Merchant. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1990., D04383030L (Box BG 39, Volume 1355)
  - Mekton
    - Mekton Empire. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1990., D04382703R (Box BG 39, Volume 1385)
    - Mekton-Operation: Rimfire. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04382689/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1384)
    - Mecha Manual 2: Invasion Terra Files. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382670U (Box BG 39, Volume 1392)
    - Mekton Plus: Advanced Technical Manual. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382707V (Box BG 39, Volume 1391)
    - Mekton Wars 1: Invasion Terra. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382690W (Box BG 39, Volume 1383)
    - Mekton Zeta. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382704S (Box BG 39, Volume 1386)
    - Mekton: Tactical Display. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04383043P (Box BG 39, Volume 1387)
    - Starblade Battalion. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1996., D04382705T (Box BG 39, Volume 1388)
  - Mercenaries, Spies, and Private Eyes
    - Mercenaries, Spies and Private Eyes. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1983., D04382753W (Box BG 39, Volume 1076)
    - Raid on Rajallapor. Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1984., D04382770V (Box BG 39, Volume 1138)
  - Middle-Earth
    - Angmar: Land of the Witch King. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1982., D04383019S (Box BG 39, Volume 1339)
    - Middle-Earth: A Campaign and Adventure Guidebook. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1982., D04383021L (Box BG 39, Volume 1341)
    - Umbar: Haven of the Corsairs. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1982., D04383017Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1337)
    - Isengard and Northern Gondor. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1983., D04383013M (Box BG 39, Volume 1333)
    - Northern Mirkwood: The Wood-Elves Realm. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1983., D04383015O (Box BG 39, Volume 1335)
    - Southern Mirkwood: Haunt of the Necromancer. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1983., D04383014N (Box BG 39, Volume 1334)
    - The Court of Ardor in Southern Middle-Earth. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1983., D04383016P (Box BG 39, Volume 1336)
    - Bree and the Barrow-Downs. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04382813T (Box BG 39, Volume 1098)
    - Dagorlad and the Dead Marshes. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04382812S (Box BG 39, Volume 1097)
    - Hillmen of the Trollshaws. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04382805U (Box BG 39, Volume 1112)
    - Middle-Earth Role Playing. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04382872Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1168)
    - Moria: The Dwarven City. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04383012L (Box BG 39, Volume 1332)
    - Rangers of the North: The Kingdom of Arthedain. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04383011K (Box BG 39, Volume 1331)
    - The Tower of Cirith Ungol and Shelob's Lair. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1984., D04382811R (Box BG 39, Volume 1096)
    - Erech and the Paths of the Dead. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04382781X (Box BG 39, Volume 1116)
    - Goblin-Gate and Eagle's Eyrie. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04382780W (Box BG 39, Volume 1115)
    - Haunted Ruins of the Dunlendings. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04382819Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1091)
    - Thieves of Tharbad. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04382806V (Box BG 39, Volume 1113)
    - Lorien and the Halls of the Elven Smiths. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1986., D04383025P (Box BG 39, Volume 1346)
    - Phantom of the Northern Marches. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1986., D04382804T (Box BG 39, Volume 1109)
    - Assassins of Dol Amroth. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382801Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1106)
    - Brigands of Mirkwood. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382785. (Box BG 39, Volume 1120)
    - Dunland and the Southern Misty Mountains. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383008Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1327)
    - Ents of Fangorn. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383009R (Box BG 39, Volume 1328)
    - Gates of Mordor. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382802R (Box BG 39, Volume 1107)
    - Havens of Gondor: Land of Belfalas. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383024O (Box BG 39, Volume 1345)
    - Lords of Middle-Earth: Vol. II: The Mannish Races. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382595- (Box BG 39, Volume 966)
    - Lost Realm of Cardolan. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382816W (Box BG 39, Volume 1088)
    - Riders of Rohan. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383018R (Box BG 39, Volume 1338)
    - Rivendell: The House of Elrond. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382807W (Box BG 39, Volume 1114)
    - Sea-Lords of Gondor. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383023N (Box BG 39, Volume 1344)
    - Weathertop: Tower of the Wind. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383007P (Box BG 39, Volume 1326)
    - Woses of the Black Wood. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04382800P (Box BG 39, Volume 1105)
    - Creatures of Middle-Earth: A Bestiary of Animals and Monsters, 1st edition. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382594Z (Box BG 39, Volume 965)
    - Far Harad: The Scorched Land. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382815V (Box BG 39, Volume 1087)
    - Halls of the Elven-King. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04383010J (Box BG 39, Volume 1330)
    - Lords of Middle-Earth: Vol. I: The Immortals, 2nd edition. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382600N (Box BG 39, Volume 970)
    - Minas Tirith. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382719Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1343)
    - Mirkwood. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382808X (Box BG 39, Volume 1093)
    - Mouths of the Entwash. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382784- (Box BG 39, Volume 1119)